[{"id": 2919, "question": "Hotel Reservations Welcome to the Kampala Beach Hotel Reservations System. You can reserve a room or package one of three ways: (a) online, (b) by phone, and(c)by email. Did you know? You can take advantage of special savings by booking direct with us online. A.Online Reservations Enter your travel dates and the number of guests below to book your room online now. Click here to check on an existing online reservation. If you are searching for a specific package, please make sure your check-in and check-out dates allowing for the minimum number of nights in the package. You may make reservations for a maximum of 4 guests per room. For requests of 10 rooms or more, please refer to Group Accommodations. B.Reservations By Phone If you prefer to reserve by phone, please call: Toll Free from the...\n\nQ: From the passage we may infer the hotel is in   _   .", "options": ["Canada", "mainland America", "French", "Hawaii"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3469, "question": "My father was poor in expressing his feelings. I knew that my dad loved me, but showed me love in other ways. There was one particular time in my life when this became real to me. I always believed that my parents had a good marriage, but gradually the strain on my mom and dad's relationship was quite evident. However, I was not prepared for the day when Dad had decided to leave. All that I could think of was that I was going to become a product of a divorced family. I kept telling myself that it wasn't going to happen. The night before he left, I stayed up in my room for a long time. I prayed and I cried and I wrote a long letter to my dad. I told him how much I loved him and that I would always and forever be his Krissie. As I folded my note, I stuck in a picture of me with a saying I ha...\n\nQ: What's the main idea of the passage?", "options": ["How the author's parents enjoyed a happy marriage.", "How a letter saved the author's parents' marriage.", "The divorce had a great influence on the author.", "The author had a good relationship with her parents."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1808, "question": "Humans may be a bad influence on their best friends---at least when it comes to problem-solving. In a task that wasn't very tough, wolves performed must better than dogs. All the animals had to do was pull the lid off a food container, containing a sausage treat. Monique Udell studies animal behavior at Oregon State University in Corvallis. She tested 10 pet dogs and another 10 dogs from an animal shelter. In one set of tests, a person was nearby but did not encourage or discourage the dogs. Those dogs typically spent 10 to 15 percent of their time gazing at the person. They spent a mere 5 percent of their time or less touching the container. Udell offered the same challenge to wolves. These animals had been raised and fed by people but still lived outdoors. Here, the wolves didn't look at...\n\nQ: What was the effect of encouragement on the dogs?", "options": ["It made their success rate improve a lot", "It made them seek less guidance", "It made them a little more devoted to the task", "It made them able to compete with the wolves"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1557, "question": "There have been many great inventions, which have changed the way we live. The first great invention was one that is still very important today---the wheel. This made it easier to carry heavy things to travel long distances. For hundreds of years there were few inventions that have made as much effect as the wheel. There was little unknown land left in the world. People didn't have to explore much any more. They began to work to make life better instead. In the second half of the 19th century many great inventions were made. Among them were the camera, the electric light and the radio. These all became a big part of our life today. The first part of the 20th century saw more great inventions. The helicopter in 1909. Sound movies in 1926. The computer in 1928, and jet planes in 1930. This w...\n\nQ: We can safely come to the conclusion that people's life will be made even better through   _  .", "options": ["new discoveries", "greater inventions", "better ways to get over diseases.", "all of above"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2566, "question": "Ten years ago,Morgan Zuch,a two--year--old girl from Long Island,New York,was diagnosed with leukemia .The day that Morgan's father Rod knew it,he made a promise,\"If my daughter gets better,I will devote the rest of my life to helping others who are in the Same condition.\" Fortunately.Morgan recovered gradually,and since then,Rod and his wife Nancy,have been helping other families with cancer.stricken children through the Morgan Center.It is the country's first preschool for children with cancer. Because of the risk of germs, children with cancer are usually forbidden from playing with other kids.They must spend their days in hospital rooms or lying in bed at home.The Zuchs believed that children with cancer should have the opportunity to play,too. The center offers the kids and their fami...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT true?", "options": ["Morgan has regained her health.", "The Center is run by the government.", "Morgan helps in the Center sometimes.", "Both kids and parents like the Center."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2760, "question": "When Danny Wallace, 26, got bored, he put an ad on the worldwide web reading simply: \"Join Me. Send a passport photo.\" A year and a half later his east London flat is the headquarters for a global internet-based \"club\" whose members carry out good deeds for strangers every Friday. It's not common for people in London to talk to strangers. If you see someone struggling with something, part of the brain goes \"I want to help\". But the trained part of the brain says: \"They will think you are mad or going to mug them\", so you walk away. Join Me now has about 3,000 members around the world who do an act of kindness every Friday. For example, I'm usually out on a Friday so I go for one of the standard acts -- the unexpected cup of coffee. You might be sitting in a cafe and see an old man in the c...\n\nQ: When Londoners see someone in trouble, they   _  .", "options": ["often give a hand", "pretend not to have seen it", "stop and ask questions", "telephone the police"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 338, "question": "John Blanchard stood up from the bench, straightened his Army uniform, and studied the crowd of people making their way through Grand Central Station. He looked for the girl whose heart he knew, but whose face he didn't, the girl with the rose. His interest in her had begun thirteen months before in a Florida library. Taking a book off the shelf he found himself intrigued, not with the words of the book, but with the notes penciled in the margin. The soft handwriting reflected a thoughtful soul and insightful mind. In the front of the book, he discovered the previous owner's name, Miss Hollis Maynell. With time and effort he located her address. She lived in New York City. He wrote her a letter introducing himself and inviting her to correspond. The next day he was shipped overseas for ser...\n\nQ: How did John Blanchard get to know Miss Hollis Maynell?", "options": ["They lived in the same city.", "They were both interested in literature.", "John knew Hollis's name from a library book.", "John came across Hollis in a Florida library."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1642, "question": "Have you ever tried broccoli ice cream? That's what Oliver serves his customers in the new movie Oliver's Organic Ice Cream. The one-minute film was created by kids. A film is a movie. The young students learned their moviemaking skills at the Jacob Burns Film Center. The center is in Pleasantville, New York. Kids who go there learn how to make movies and music videos. The character Oliver and his treats are animated. In an animated movie, objects, such as ice cream and paper dolls, appear to be alive or moving. Animated movies are made up of hundreds of pictures. It takes 15 pictures to make just one second of film. To make a movie that lasts one minute, students need to take about 900 frames. A frame is a picture. Animation expert Joe Summerhays teaches kids the steps to shoot a movie. H...\n\nQ: What would be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Movie magic", "Organic ice cream", "Jacob Burns Film Center", "One-minute film"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2781, "question": "Elephants scored a big win in Dohar, Qatar, on March 22, 2010. Representatives from 175 countries met in the Middle Eastem country. They voted to continue a ban on the sale of ivory . Two African nations, Tanzania and Zambia, had asked to open up the ivory trade. People feared that weakening a 21-year-old ban on the sale of ivory would encourage illegal hunting and hurt elephant populations. African elephants once numbered in the millions. Today, there are fewer than 500,000. \"People born in 100 years should be able to see an elephant,\" said Noah Wekesa, Kenya's minister of forest and wildlife. His country voted to keep the ban. In the 1980s, as many as 1 million elephants were killed throughout Africa. Hunters killed the animals for their ivory tusks, which were used to make jewelry and o...\n\nQ: The text is mainly about   _  .", "options": ["continuing a ban on the ivory sale to protect elephants", "protecting endangered animals around the world", "the effects of the ivory wars of the 1980s", "the life of elephants in the wild"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 96, "question": "Owning a smartphone may not be as smart as you think.They may let you surf the Internet,listen to music and snap photos wherever you are...but they also turn you into a workaholic,it seems.A study suggests that,by giving you access to emails at all times.the all-singing.all-dancing mobile phone adds as much as two hours to your working day. Researchers found that Britons work an additional 460hours a year on average as they are able to respond to emails on their mobiles.The study by technology retailer Pixmania,reveals the average UK working day is between nine and ten hours,but a further two hours is spent responding to or sending work emails,or making work calls.Almost one in ten admits spending up to three hours outside their normal working day checking work emails.Some workers confess ...\n\nQ: Ghadi may agree that  _  .", "options": ["employees are supposed to be on call 24 hours a day", "the ability to access many apps made smartphones worthless", "smartphones might turn a person into a workaholic", "people literally cannot get away from work without smartphones"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1040, "question": "Do dogs understand us? Be careful what you say around your dog. It might understand more than you think. A _ named Rico recognizes the names of about 200 objects, say researchers in Germany. The dog also appears to be able to learn new words as easily as a 3-year-old child. Its word-learning skills are as good as those of a parrot or _ . In one experiment, the researchers took all 200 items that Rico is supposed to know and divided them into 20 groups of 10 objects. Then the owner told the dog to go and fetch one of the items and bring it back. In four tests, Rico got 37 out of 40 commands right. As the dog couldn't see anyone to get clues, the scientists believe Rico must understand the meanings of certain words. In another experiment, the scientists took one toy that Rico had never seen ...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is true?", "options": ["The purpose of the experiments is to show the border collie's mental abilities.", "Rico has a better memory partly because of its proper early training.", "The border collie is world-famous for recognizing objects.", "Rico is born to understand its owner's commands."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2063, "question": "It was time for a school holiday and I was at home. My family's house was located in an area by the sea. I just sat down in front of the television. Suddenly I heard a loud noise and then the first shock started to hit. My mom and I ran to the front door. We got out and we were standing in the street holding on to each other to stand up. The ground was covered with snow. I could remember watching black cracks in the earth snaking their way along the ground. A tree in our back yard was actually cut in half. As suddenly as the earthquake started, it was over. Dead silence. Then a light snow began to fall. All the power was off--no radio, no TV and no communication with the outside world. We found out later that the ground area was lowered an average of 35 feet. My dad succeeded in getting ho...\n\nQ: What would be the best title of the passage?", "options": ["My father", "My mother and I", "A quake in my town", "Earthquake tips"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1275, "question": "In 1974, after filling out fifty applications, going through four interviews, and winning one offer, I took what I could get ----- a teaching job at what I considered a distant wild area: western New Jersey. My characteristic optimism was alive only when I reminded myself that I would be doing what I had wanted to do since I was fourteen ------- teaching English. School started, but I felt more and more as if I were in a foreign country. Was this rural area really New Jersey? My students took a week off when hunting season began. I was told they were also frequently absent in late October to help their fathers make hay on the farms. I was a young woman from New York City, who thought that \"Make hay while the sun shines\" just meant to have a good time. But, still, I was teaching English. I ...\n\nQ: It can be inferred from the story that in 1974    _   .", "options": ["the writer became an optimistic person", "it was rather difficult to get a job in the USA", "the writer was very happy about her new job", "it was easy to get a teaching job in New Jersey"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2342, "question": "Whales live in the ocean, but they are not fish. They are warm-blooded mammals and must have air to breathe. The babies are born alive and drink milk from the mother's body. It took millions of years for the whale to develop as it is today. Every spring groups of whales swim hundreds of kilometers to warm places to bear their young. Each group goes to the same place every year. The mothers take very good care of their babies. The fully grown whales are very gentle and playful with each other, and with humans. They \"talk\" to each other with a high noise that sounds beautiful. This\"talking\" can be heard for more than 300 kilometers in open waters. Yet humans kill over a hundred whales a day. They kill them to make whale oils and a lot of other things. Killing them is a modern business with m...\n\nQ: Every year humans kill    _    all over the world.", "options": ["nearly forty thousand whales", "less than four million", "about four thousand whales", "about fourteen thousand whales"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2044, "question": "When a child is told he is \"uncool\", it can be very painful. He may say he doesn't care, and even act in ways that are opposite of cool on purpose. But ultimately, these are simply ways to handle sadness by pretending it's not there. Helping a child feel better in school had to be careful. If you say, \"Why are you worried about what other children think about you? It doesn't matter!\" Children know that it does matter. Instead, an active way may be best. You could say, \"I'm going to do a couple of things for you to help you feel better in school.\" If a boy is having trouble making friends, the teacher can help him. The teacher can arrange things so that he has chances to use his abilities to contribute to class projects. This is how the other children learn how to value his good qualities a...\n\nQ: A child who has been informed of being \"uncool\" may   _  .", "options": ["care nothing about it", "develop a sense of anger", "do something uncool purposely", "pretend to get hurt very much"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 94, "question": "According to Andrew, it never would have happened if he had not had a flat tire on Highway 10 last night at about 7:30. He was on his way to attend a three-day sales meeting when he had the flat. tyre. Unfortunately, he did not have a spare, so he pushed the car off the road, locked it up, and managed to thumb a ride back to Pine Grove. It was after eleven o'clock when he finally got home, and it was then that his real problems started. When Andrew left home at about 5:30, he had told his wife not to expect him back until Thursday or Friday. Knowing that his wife was nervous about staying in the house alone at night, Andrew took the precaution of checking all the windows in the house to be sure they were locked, so that he could report to his wife that the house was secure. He convinced hi...\n\nQ: Why did the police officers take Andrew off to jail?", "options": ["It was too late for them to contact Andrew's wife.", "Andrew did not explain clearly why he broke into the house.", "They thought it unnecessary to check Andrew's story.", "they concluded that Andrew's story was a complete invention."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2489, "question": "They tell us when to get up or when we're running late for work and whether we are in danger of missing our favourite TV programme. But while our daily routines rely on clocks that tell us the time, science is discovering that our well-being is influenced by a very different kind of timepiece. Circadian rhythms---the human body's own internal clock---have a powerful influence on our health and behaviour. _ are programmed from birth and control functions ranging from temperature and blood pressure to sleep patterns. In recent years researchers have also discovered that this built-in mechanism can influence everything from the way we react to medicines to how well we learn music. The latest example, from experts at Harvard University in the US, shows that the human body clock can even dictat...\n\nQ: What is the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Rebuild your body clock", "Timing is everything", "Sleep more, lie less", "Your time is limited"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3265, "question": "Dreams can be familiar and strange, fantastical or boring, but some dreams might be connected to the mental processes that help us learn. In a recent study, scientists found a connection between nap-time dreams and better memory in people who were learning a new skill. In the study,99 college students between the ages of 18 and 30 each spent an hour on a compute, trying to get through a virtual maze .The maze was different place each time they tired--making it even more difficult. They were also told to find a particular picture of a tree and remember where it was. For the first 90 minutes of a five-hour break, half of the participants stayed awake and an half were told to take a short nap .Participants who stayed awake were asked to describe their thoughts. Participants who took a nap wer...\n\nQ: What is the best title for this text?", "options": ["Dreams Are Strange", "Not All Dreams Are True", "Dreaming Makes Perfect", "Stickgold, a Dream Expert"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2249, "question": "Experts say that students usually need eight to ten hours' sleep at night, but most Chinese students do not get enough sleep. Some Chinese parents are usually glad to see their children study late. They will think their children work very hard. But not all parents are happy about this. Once a mother told us that every morning her 10-year-old boy put up one finger with his eyes still closed, begging for one more minute to sleep. Like thousands of students \"early birds\" in China, he has to get up before six every morning. A report shows that without a good night's sleep, students seem to be weaker than they should be. Many students have fallen asleep during class at one time or another. Too much homework is not the only reason why students stay up late. Some watch TV or play the computer gam...\n\nQ: Many students have fallen asleep in class because   _  .", "options": ["they have too much homework to do at night", "they watch TV late", "they play the computer games late into the night", "all of the above"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1832, "question": "Being young is great. Most of the parts of your body still work great, you have a full head of hair, you're energetic, and you have a world of opportunity in front of you. However, there's going to come a time when you start to get older. And as you get older, you'll have new responsibilities, complete independence, and perhaps most importantly, less time to recover from mistakes. You see, we all make mistakes in life. Maybe you spent more money than you should have on a car, you passed up on a great job opportunity, or you didn't try as hard as you could have in school. It's a part of life and we learn from it. But there are certain mistakes that are much better made while you're still young and have plenty of time to recover. I'm definitely not telling you that you should purposely go ou...\n\nQ: What does the author really mean by saying \"it's a lot better to take risks when you're younger\"?", "options": ["You should purposely go out and make these mistakes so that you can learn from them and not have them ruin your entire life.", "There are certain mistakes that are much better made while you're still young and have plenty of time to recover.", "When you get older, you'll have rich experiences to share with your friends and families however dumb you were", "The younger you start, the fewer risks you can withstand and still come out with a positive return."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2932, "question": "Jones worked so hard that made the sparks fly from his hammer.The son of Mr.Smith, a rich neighbor, used to come to see the blacksmith and he would enjoy himself watching how the tradesman worked.\"Why don't you try your hand to learn to make shoe tacks?\" said the blacksmith.\"Who knows, one day, it may be of use to you.\" The lazy boy began to see what he could do.But after a little practice he found that he was becoming very skilled and soon he was making some of the finest tacks. Old Mr.Smith died and the son on account of the war lost all his goods.He had to leave home and was forced to take up residence in another country.It so happened that in this village there were numerous shoemakers who were spending a lot of money to buy tacks for their shoes and even at times when they paid high p...\n\nQ: Which of the following well-known sayings can best tell the main idea of the passage?", "options": ["Knowledge is no burden.", "Where there's a will, there's a way.", "You can't teach an old dog new tricks.", "Time lost cannot be recalled."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1016, "question": "BEIJING--Seven prestigious universities in China announced Sunday that they would begin using the same independent exam --besides the national one --to test students hoping to gain entrance to them in 2011. The seven are Peking University, Beihang University, Beijing Normal University, Nankai University, Fudan University, Xiamen University and Hong Kong University. Students who want to gain entrance to any of the seven universities will only have to sit one independent exam, according to the joint announcement. \"This will help lighten the students' load, otherwise they must take several exams for different universities ,\"said the announcement. Passing the exam could result in more than one interview chance, giving the students more opportunities to choose their favorite universities. China...\n\nQ: What is the advantage of universities selecting students according to independent examinations?", "options": ["Students needn't take the national exam.", "Students 'education cost can be lowered.", "Students' abilities and talents can be better found.", "It can encourage middle schools to recommend more qualified students."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1529, "question": "We know that the earth has become warmer over the last century. The Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC), a group established by the World Meteorological Organization and the United Nations Environment Program, reports that the average surface temperature of the earth has increased during the twentieth century by 0.6deg _ 0.2degC.(The _ 0.2degC means that the increase might be as small as 0.4degC or as great as 0.8degC). This may seem like a small shift, but although regional and short--term temperatures do fluctuate over a wide range, global temperatures are generally quite stable. In fact, the difference between today's average global temperature and the average global temperature during the last Ice Age is only about 5 degrees C. Indeed, it's warmer today around the world th...\n\nQ: What would be the best title for this text?", "options": ["What Are the Scientific Disagreements", "You Can Think of This Website", "What Do We Know about Global Climate Change?", "The Vast Majority of Climate Researchers"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2323, "question": "Catherine and I were on our way to our nephew's birthday party one rainy Saturday morning, driving along what some people call moose alley. It was early, there were few other cars on the road and we were looking forward to a good day with the family. Suddenly, a moose rushed across our path. Fortunately, a quick swerve to the other lane prevented a full impact, with only a small collision on the right side of our car ripping off the mirror and knocking the moose to the pavement. By the time I stopped and looked back in my rear view mirror, the moose was getting up. It ran into the bush. Shaken but unharmed, we both looked at each other shocked by what had happened. We knew that moose accidents had claimed many lives throughout the years, and that we had been very fortunate to escape with n...\n\nQ: What did the accident teach the author?", "options": ["Being open to unexpected turns in life is important.", "Life is long if you know how to use it.", "Life is measured by thoughts and actions, not by time.", "Life is unpredictable, so we should treasure every moment."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1889, "question": "A brother and sister have been reunited after more than 60 years, thanks to a letter in the Welwyn and Hatfield Times. For years John Hannant Kept a photograph of his long-lost sister, hoping they would meet again. Margery, the eldest of the three children, had signed up to the Royal Air Force as part of the war effort, when John was still a baby. The family lost touch and as the decade s passed only a single letter gave a clue to her whereabouts. The clue was enough for a WHT reader to recognize Margery and put the family back in touch.. John, 67, had been searching for a long time and a friend suggested writing to the paper. \"That's the one that made it, the letter to the paper a few months age,\" he said. \"It's like a dream come true. The last time we ever heard from Margery was in 1953 ...\n\nQ: What do we know about Jack Cooke's family?", "options": ["Jack now has a son and a daughter.", "Jack and his wife live with their children now", "Jack's wife is in good health all the time.", "Jack lost touch with his family a long time ago."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1609, "question": "My father never wanted his children to know what he did for a living.Dad worked in Plant C.Lying beside lake Erie, it saw him in at sunrise and out at nightfall.Sometimes my mother would take my siblings and me to the public beach in our hometown of Ashtabula.she'd gather us round.and point to the smokestacks, coughing clouds into the sky. \"Wave to daddy!\" she'd shout. Four little hands would shoot into the air. I never knew what Dad did in Plant C, but during 34 years of hard work, he had surgery on his shoulder and hand. At 48, he had his first heart attack. He retired in 1993, right after the last kid graduated from college.But the damage was done.A few years later, the next heart attack killed him. I saw my dad in Plant C only once, when l took dinner to him. That night, I looked at my...\n\nQ: The author gave her daughter the hat to hope that her daughter cold  _  .", "options": ["remember her grandfather", "overcome all difficulties by wearing it", "get encouraged by her grandfather", "follow her grandfather' s work"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 900, "question": "\"Mommy, I'm a funny bird,\" Jack, my almost-4-year-old tells me. He moves his little fingers like wings. \"You are?\" I say. I'm sitting across from him while he eats breakfast at our table. I smile; he says the greatest things. A week ago, however, when he had chocolate on his face and I licked my finger to wipe it off, he said, \"Don't put your dirty water on me.\" A week ago, I wouldn't have been sitting here with him during breakfast. I wouldn't have been up, emptying the dishwasher, cleaning the kitchen, or answering emails. We always had dinner together at the table, but other meals got much less attention. I work from home, and my husband owns an advertising agency and often travels. We were so busy that we had to do the chores during breakfast or lunch. Why was I not sitting down with m...\n\nQ: Before visiting the friends, Jack   _  .", "options": ["didn't like chocolate", "couldn't eat by himself", "was sometimes rude to his mom", "preferred his mother to his father"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1424, "question": "The Internet has led to a huge increase in credit-card fraud.Your card information can even be on sale on an illegal website.Websites offering cheap goods and services should be regarded with care.Online shoppers who enter their credit-card information may never receive the goods they thought they had bought. The thieves then go shopping with your card number--or sell the information over the Internet.Computer hackers have broken down security system, raising questions about the safety of card holder information. Several months ago, 25,000 customers of a CD universe, an online music retailer , were not lucky.Their names, addresses and credit-card numbers were posted on a Website after the retailer refused to pay $ 157,828 to get back the information.Credit-card firms are now fighting again...\n\nQ: What's the best title of the passage?", "options": ["How to Beat Online Credit-card Thieves", "How to Shop on the Internet", "Never Use Credit-card Without an Advanced Compute", "Why Thieves Steal Credit-card Information"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2518, "question": "A young man went to a town and worked there. He did not have a wife and a servant did the work in his house. The young man liked laughing a lot. He nailed the servant's shoes to the floor on Monday, and then laughed, because he put his feet in them and fell down. The servant was not angry, but smiled. Then the young man put brushes in his bed on Tuesday. The servant got into bed and hit the brushes with his feet. He was afraid. The young man laughed loudly again. Again the servant was not angry, but smiled. Then on Wednesday the young man said to his servant, \"You're a nice, kind man. I am not going to be unkind to you again.\" The servant smiled and said, \"And I'm not going to put any more mud from the street in your coffee.\"...\n\nQ: He played a joke on the servant because   _  .", "options": ["he hated him", "he was not satisfied with the food the servant prepared for him", "he wanted to get pleasure", "he liked to show off himself"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1528, "question": "We know that the earth has become warmer over the last century. The Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC), a group established by the World Meteorological Organization and the United Nations Environment Program, reports that the average surface temperature of the earth has increased during the twentieth century by 0.6deg _ 0.2degC.(The _ 0.2degC means that the increase might be as small as 0.4degC or as great as 0.8degC). This may seem like a small shift, but although regional and short--term temperatures do fluctuate over a wide range, global temperatures are generally quite stable. In fact, the difference between today's average global temperature and the average global temperature during the last Ice Age is only about 5 degrees C. Indeed, it's warmer today around the world th...\n\nQ: We know from the text that carbon dioxide   _  .", "options": ["is one of the most important greenhouse gases", "has fossil fuels", "traps cold near the planet's surface", "exist in human activities"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2595, "question": "Parties held by the wealthy seldom welcome poor guests.But last week China made it through the doors into a gathering of the world's richest countries. Jin Renqing ,Chian's finance minister,and Zhou Xiaochuan,governor of the People's Bank of China,joined a meeting of the Group of Seven(G7)on October1,2004.It is the fist time that China has had direct talks with the club.It was a good chance to share the world powers'thoughts about critical economic issues and _ understanding. China'a participation is a natural part of its increasingly important role in the global economy.China is the world 's factory and the biggest market. America and China made up almost half of global economic growth last year.\"If Anerican consumers and Chinese producers were to reduce their activities at the same time,...\n\nQ: According to the passage,China particpates in the meeting of G7 because  _  .", "options": ["China has become one of the richest countries of the world", "China is playing a more important part in the world economy", "China has more factories than any other countries in the world", "developing countries want China to speak for them"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3181, "question": "Instagram is a fast,beautiful and fun way to share your life with friends and family.Take a picture or video,choose a filter to transform its look and feel.and then post to Instagram--it's that easy.You can even share to Facebook.Twitter and more.It's a new way to see the world.So many photos of food are contained on Instagram--now a pop-up diner in London is taking advantage of this new trend by letting people settle the bill for their meals simply by uploading photos of their dishes to social networks. I always thought people's taking pictures of their food was kind of silly, but at this new pop-up restaurant in the UK,I'd probably do it too.\"The Picture House\"is the world's first pay-by-photo restaurant--you order, click a photo of the food,share on Instagram and eat for free! The resta...\n\nQ: Instagram probably is  _  .", "options": ["a restaurant free of chmge", "a campaign of\"Food for Life''", "a program used to share photos", "a new marketing project"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1195, "question": "Harvard researchers have created a tough, low-cost, biodegradable material inspired by insects' hard outer shells. The material's inventors say it has a number of possible uses and someday could provide a more environmentally friendly alternative to plastic. The material, made from shrimp (') shells and proteins produced from silk, is called \"shrilk.\" It is thin, clear, flexible and strong. A major benefit of the material is its biodegradability. Plastic's toughness and flexibility represented a revolution in materials science during the 1950s and '60s. Decades later, however, plastic's very durability is raising questions about how appropriate it is for one-time products such as plastic bags, or short-lived consumer goods, used in the home for a few years and then cast into a landfill whe...\n\nQ: What are the inventors doing in the lab?", "options": ["Replacing carbon fibers with shrilk.", "Testing ahrilk's use in wet conditions.", "Making shrilk out of used household goods.", "Improving shrilk's flexibility for medical purposes."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 773, "question": "Attitude is an internal state that influences the choices of personal action made by the individual . Some researchers consider that attitudes come from differences between beliefs and ideas; others believe that attitudes come from emotional states. Here, we focus on the effects of attitudes upon behavior, that is, upon the choices of action made by the individual. The kinds of actions taken by human beings are obviously influenced greatly by attitudes. Whether one listens to classical music or rock, whether one obeys the speed limit while driving, whether one encourages one's husband or wife to express his or her own ideas-all are influenced by attitudes. These internal states are acquired throughout life from situations one is faced with in the home, in the streets, and in the school. Of...\n\nQ: What would be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Differences of Attitudes.", "Nature of Attitude.", "Choices of Attitudes.", "Changes of Attitude."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3045, "question": "I grow up in San Pedro. My Dad was a fisherman, and he loved the sea. He had his own boat, but it was hard making a living on the sea. He worked hard and would stay out until he caught enough to feed the family. Not just enough for our family, but also for his Mom and Dad and the other kids that were still at home. Dad was a big man, and he was strong from pulling the nets and fighting the sea for his catch. When you got close to him, you smelled the ocean. When the weather was bad he would drive me to school. He would pull right up in front, and it seemed like everybody would be standing around and watching. Then he would lean over and give me a big kiss on the cheek and tell me to be a good boy. It was so embarrassing for me. Here I was twelve years old, and my Dad would lean over and ki...\n\nQ: From the passage, we know that the writer's father   _  .", "options": ["was a successful businessman", "had an accident and died at sea", "was good at driving cars", "drove the writer to school every day"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1594, "question": "Narasimha Das is on his way to feed 169,379 hungry children. Das is in charge of a kitchen in Vrindaban. The town is about a three-hour drive from India's capital, New Delhi. Das gets to work at 3:00 a.m. Thirty workers are already working to make tens of thousands of rounds of bread. It will be brought to 1,516 schools in and around Vrindaban. A Growing Problem Going to school is difficult for more than 13 million children in India. They must go to work instead, or go hungry. That's why India began the Mid-Day Meal Scheme, the largest school-lunch program in the world. A free lunch encourages children to come to school and gives them the energy they need for learning. The program began in the 1960s. The kitchen in Vrindaban is run by the Akshaya Patra Foundation. It is one of the lunch pr...\n\nQ: The kitchen in Vrindaban supplies food to   _  .", "options": ["the poor", "the old", "college students", "school children"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 302, "question": "Beginning college is exciting: new ideas to explore, new challenges to be met and many decisions to be made; your future begins here. However, you will find college life is different from your previous school environment. Many of us can be easily overwhelmed by the details of running a well-balanced life. While some of us may have the know-how, I guess there are more of us who can benefit from learning about the experiences of others who have walked the college halls before you. The following you may find of use about life on campus: *Plan well. There are so many new things to do at a new college or university. Give yourself time to make new friends and became familiar with the campus, but don't forget why you are there. Give some time for social activities and manage your time wisely. *If...\n\nQ: What is the main purpose of the passage?", "options": ["To offer advice on college life.", "To explain why college life is exciting.", "To describe the importance of college life.", "To persuade you to go to college."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2803, "question": "Child labor -- the employment of children in industry, often against their will -- has been a problem for many years. Over a hundred years ago, Charles Dickens shocked many of his readers when he described the conditions under which young children worked in British factories. The conditions Dickens described continue almost unchanged today in many parts of the world. The only difference is that today employment of children is confined(limited)to small industries and family businesses, such as hotels, restaurants and particularly farms, rather than to large factories. Girls suffer more from child labor practices than boys. Many of them are forced to start work when they are only ten years old. Although the work they are given to do is often light, it is often harmful to the health. Recently...\n\nQ: Young children go to work   _  .", "options": ["because they are forced to", "in order to be skillful in a certain kind of work", "in order to be paid well", "in order to earn money for education"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 707, "question": "Children grow quickly, especially their feet, but many families cannot buy new shoes each time a child needs them. As a result, about 300 million children around the world go barefoot. Those children risk picking up diseases and parasites from the soil. An American man may have a solution for those barefoot kids -- a shoe that grows with the child. Kenton Lee is the creator of The Shoe That Grows. He explains how the shoe works and how it is able to last so long. \"It grows in three places: the front; it can also grow on the side with Velcro; and on the back with our buckle. It can last up to five years. The bottom is compressed rubber like tire rubber. The top is just high-quality leather.\" The shoe comes in two sizes: small that fits children aged 4 to 9 and large for children aged 9 to 1...\n\nQ: Which of the following is the characteristic of the newly invented shoes?", "options": ["They are more expensive.", "They are not so comfortable.", "They can grow with a child.", "They come in different sizes."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1997, "question": "When Carlos Westez died at the age of 76, a language died, too. Westez, more commonly known as Red Thunder Cloud, was the last speaker of the Native American language, Catawba.www.ks5u.com Anyone who wants to hear various songs of the Catawba tribe can get in touch with the Smithsonian Institution in Washington, D.C., where, back in the 1940s, Red Thunder Cloud recorded a series of songs for future generations. They are all that is left of the Catawba language. The language that people used to speak is gone forever. We are all aware of the damage that modern industry can do to the world's ecology. However, few people are aware of the effect that widely spoken languages have on other languages and ways of life. English has spread all over the world. Chinese, Spanish, Russian, and Hindi have...\n\nQ: What do we learn about Red Thunder Cloud?", "options": ["He passed away in the 1940s.", "He was born into the Catawba tribe.", "He learned Catawba from his mother.", "He used to visit the Catawba reservation often."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2873, "question": "Both are so much related to each other. And both are so dissimilar! What are the differences between friendship and love? Is platonic friendship possible between persons of opposite sex? Let us try and understand. What is friendship? Why do we call a person our friend? When do we call someone a very good friend? If we care for a person, if we are always ready to help that person and if we share most of our thoughts with a person, they are our good friends. We can always count upon our good friends in an emergency. We are always sure that our friend will understand why we acted in a certain way. We need not explain anything to our very good friends. The friendship is so deep and the relationship is so close, that most of the things are automatically understood by our friends. What about lov...\n\nQ: If you are friends, you'll   _  .", "options": ["dream of him at night", "lie awake at night and think your friend", "feel you don't meet him for a long time", "never feel excited meeting your friend"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2237, "question": "Once upon a time two brothers who lived on neighbouring farms fell into conflict. It was the first serious one in 40 years of farming side by side, sharing machinery, and trading labor and goods as needed . Then the long cooperoration fell apart. It began with a small misunderstanding and it grew into a major difference, and finally it exploded into an exchange of bitter words followed by weeks of silence. One morning there was a knock on John's door. He opened it to find a man with a carpenter's toolbox. \"I'm looking for a few days' work\" he said. \"Perhaps you would have a few small jobs here and there I could help with. Could I help you?\" \"Yes,\" said the older brother. \"I do have a job for you. Look across the creek at that farm. That's my neighbor, in fact, it's my younger brother. Last...\n\nQ: What was the life for the two brothers before the conflict ?", "options": ["They live a poor , miserable life .", "They were friendly neighbours ,helping each other .", "They never speak to each other .", "They live together as one family."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2322, "question": "One of the most famous basketball-players in the New Castle's history was paralyzed in a wheelchair one day...and was walking the next. Citizens of New Castle simply refer to it as \"The Miracle\". Joel Haler woke up in his dorm room at Hope College last October totally paralyzed from the waist down. Four hospitals later, the only way he could walk was through Robotic Walking Treatment. \"This past Tuesday, I was doing the Robotic walk and lasted ten minutes,\" Joel said. After that, he gave up. Joel wanted to accept the inevitable and cancelled his next Robotic Walking Treatment appointment. Then, the night before his cancelled appointment, he woke up to a terrible pain. An hour and a half later, the serious pain left him with an unusual feeling in his legs. \"As it continued to move up my leg...\n\nQ: Before Joel Haler's walking again, his attitude to the illness was_.", "options": ["positive", "indifferent", "optimistic", "hopeless"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2386, "question": "International Schools Services Experience teaching overseas Have you thought of working overseas? International Schools Services is looking for teachers for thousands of positions.Schools are looking for experienced, well-trained persons who must meet two of the three criteria: *A four-year bachelor's degree *Certification in a subject *Two years' successful teaching experience in a public or private school Attend one of our International Recruitment Conferences .Hundreds of schools will be available.Over 2,000 positions are expected to be filled. *Atlanta--December 4,201 1--December 6, 2011 *Bangkok--January 4, 2012~January 7, 2012 *Boston--February 5, 2012~February 9, 2012 *San Francisco--February 13, 2012~February 16, 2012 Becoming an international educator will offer you a journey you ...\n\nQ: Which would be the best choice to fill in the blank in the passage?", "options": ["Have an unforgettable journey", "Earn a good salary overseas", "Meet new people overseas", "Accept the opportunity of a lifetime"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1022, "question": "Did the iPod kill music ? DID Steve Jobs kill the music industry? That's the question on many people's lips since rock star Jon Bon Jovi accused the apple boss of personally destroying the music industry. Bon Jovi centers his criticism on how he believes music downloading has robbed young people of what he calls the \"beauty of buying on album\", \"Kids today have missed the beauty of taking your allowance money and making a decision based on the _ , not knowing what the record sounded like,\" he said. But far from killing the industry, many young people today think Jobs has been a blessing , offering you instant, and selective access to a whole world of music. Keith Staskiewicz at Entertainment Weekly speaks for the feelings of many music lovers. He believes listening to Mp3s rather than reco...\n\nQ: Jon Bon Jovi thinks Steve Jobs has destroyed the music industry because   _  .", "options": ["Apple encourages illegal music downloading", "children today prefer music downloading to buying albums", "children today do not like to discover new music", "children don't care what a record sounds like"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 22, "question": "Today, whether or not you follow the latest trends, one's fashion and choice of dress is a reflection of one's individual style and tastes. Can you still remember how you dressed at the start of China's opening-up? Today's program is one of a special series commemorating the 30th anniversary of reform and opening-up in China. In these two episodes we focused on fashion and style and were honored to invite two special guests to join us in studio--Ms. Zhang Ling from Raffles-BICT Inter-national College and Alex from Esquire magazine. When we talk about fashion, color is absolutely crucial. A color can reflect the mood of an individual person or the spiritual temperament of entire society or age. Mrs. Zhang and Alex talked about the colors which have left the greatest impression on them. In t...\n\nQ: The fact that many luxury brands have flocked into China shows that   _  .", "options": ["China has given up its own culture", "Chinese have been tired of array of vivid colors in the markets", "Chinese have increased their disposable income and purchasing power", "China has grown tired of its traditional brands"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2533, "question": "As computers become more popular in China , Chinese people are increasingly relying on computer keyboards to input Chinese characters . But if they use the computer too much , they may end up forgetting the exact strokes of each Chinese character when writing on paper . Experts suggest people , especially students , write by hand more . Do you write by hand more or type more ? In Beijing , students start using a computer as early as primary school . And computer dependence is more widespread among university students . Almost all their assignments and essays are typed on a computer . All the students interviewed say they usually use a computer . It's faster and easier to correct if using a computer . And that's why computers are being applied more and more often to modern education . But w...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is NOT true of the advantages of handwriting ?", "options": ["Handwriting contains the writer's emotion .", "The writer's thinking and personality are shown in his or her handwriting .", "Handwriting can impress people well and build one's self-confidence .", "Chinese characters enjoy both practical and aesthetic value ."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 964, "question": "Every fall, many Jewish people around the world celebrate the holiday of Sukkot . They build huts in their backyards, and if it is warm and dry outside, they live in those huts for seven days and nights. Living in a sukkah is meant to remind Jewish people that for 40 years their ancestors lived in huts in the desert. In modern times, it has also become a reminder that many people do not have a place to call home. In 2010, an American reporter named Hoshua Foer was building his own sukkah when he came up with an idea. He wondered what it would be like to have a competition for people around the world to use their imaginations to create modern sukkahs. It would be a design competition. But the sukkah would have to be built according to Jewish laws. These laws are found in an ancient book cal...\n\nQ: What's the passage mainly about?", "options": ["How Jewish people design and build modern sukkahs.", "How Jewish people celebrate the holiday of Sukkot.", "A Jewish holiday reminds people of their ancestors.", "A Jewish tradition becomes the idea for a competition."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2456, "question": "After 10 seasons wearing the No.8 on his back, Kobe Bryant will become No.24 next season. The reason for the surprising decision by the Los Angeles Lakers super guard last week has become a hot topic for debate. Bryant wore No.24 when he was in early high school, but he changed to No.33 in his senior year. He switched to No.8 when he was selected by the Lakers in 1996, and has been not changed since. Bryant has refused to explain the decision until the end of the play-offs. So guessing Bryant's motive has become a popular game among NBA fans and newspaper columnists. There are all kinds of speculations . Many say that Bryant wants to leave the past behind and have a fresh start. He has often been criticized for playing to benefit himself and not the team as a whole. Others say that he may ...\n\nQ: Bryant plays for   _  .", "options": ["The Los Angels Lakers", "TheHoustonrockets", "The ChicagoBulls", "TheMiamiHeats"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3248, "question": "Italy is one country where beauty is prized more than any other virtue. That is, except in the small town of Piobbico, the self-declared World Capital of Ugly People. The road sign at the edge of the town even warns visitors that they are entering the ugly zone. People who consider themselves ugly have been gathering in Piobbico since the 1960s. That's when Ugly Club president Telesforo Lacobelli established a dating agency for women who believed they were too ugly to attract husbands. Lacobelli believes that he is ugly himself because he has a short nose in a country where long or large noses have always been considered beautiful. People from around the world travel to Piobbico to tell their sad stories of ugliness. During the annual Festival of the Ugly, which occurs on the first Sunday ...\n\nQ: Which of the following would be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["The Ugly Capital of the World", "The Ugliest Person of the World", "Festival of the Ugly", "Beauty Contests Should be Banned"], "answer": 0}]